http://www.cablelabs.com/privacy-policy/

Follow us
CableLabs, including its subsidiaries Kyrio, Kyrio Medical, and UpRamp, are committed to protecting your privacy and personal data and this notice sets forth information about how we collect, use, process, and transfer personal data and sets forth your privacy rights. We understand the importance of personal privacy and we take our role protecting those interests seriously. This Privacy Notice reflects both current U.S. laws and the European General Data Protection Regulation.
Through our strong partnerships with members, vendors, customers, startups, and researchers across the industry, CableLabs influences the technology we use today and creates the technology of tomorrow. CableLabs, Kyrio, Kyrio Medical, and UpRamp, while legally separate corporations, work together in concert to deliver the future of connectivity. This Privacy Notice applies to CableLabs and each of its subsidiaries.
Information privacy and personal data collection, norms, and laws change over time and, accordingly, we may update this Privacy Notice as we undertake new personal data practices or adopt new privacy policies.
How We Collect Your Data, What Data We Collect, and What We Do with It
CableLabs and its subsidiaries collect the following personal data in accord with the use purposes explained further in this policy: your business email address, phone number, and address as you disclose in the normal course of business with CableLabs or a subsidiary. This data collection is necessary for the performance of CableLabs’ contractual obligation to its members. This obligation extends to Kyrio, Kyrio Medical, and UpRamp as these entities are promoted with CableLabs and work together in providing innovation to the cable industry and in the commercialization of these innovations. This information is processed to provide you with newsletters, conference information, seminars, webinars, and other information from CableLabs, Kyrio, Kyrio Medical, and UpRamp that will be beneficial or otherwise assist you in your work.
This data is collected when you work with CableLabs or a subsidiary, submit devices for certifications, attend conferences, interact with our websites by leaving feedback or comments on content, such as articles, videos, and blog posts, and communicate with CableLabs with regards to these or other activities. Unless you provide specific information about yourself when you interact with us online, we will only capture general data analytics which do not specifically identify you. If you are involved in certain projects or certification specification development activities, CableLabs uses your personal information to comply with policies and procedures, legal and accreditation requirements. CableLabs must capture your personal data for these purposes, and provide information about activities related to project, or certification specification development groups in which you participate. Participation may be documented through various methods, e.g., rosters, submission documents, email reflectors, records of meeting attendance, responses to surveys, questionnaires or ballots, participation lists, and declaration of affiliations.
CableLabs will also receive your information through your participation in CableLabs or subsidiary operated programs. For example, when you fill out an application to apply to the UpRamp Fiterator® accelerator program, we may use this information to work with you as part of the Fiterator accelerator program, whether as an actual or potential cohort group member, mentor, or presenter. We also may receive your information through other means, such as when you provide it to us by giving us your business card or through attending an event (e.g. pitch events, CableLabs or a subsidiary conference or webinar). CableLabs may occasionally receive your information from third parties, such as third-party conference providers, as part of attendance/sponsorship of a conference. This data collection is necessary so that CableLabs may work with you and provide you information on projects, certification activity, and events.
In association with attending a CableLabs or subsidiary hosted conference or event, you may have the option to download a mobile conference app to help you navigate the conference and plan your schedule. This conference app may require the device identifier associated with your device but does not collect or use any other personal data. If you are a presenter at one of our conferences, then we will collect information about you including your name, employer and contact information. If approved through your written consent, we may also collect photographs, make and store video and/or audio recordings of your presentation.
Please note that we do not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive information from children. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child, please contact us.
CableLabs, Kyrio, Kyrio Medical, and UpRamp do not sell personal data to anyone and only share it with third parties who are facilitating the delivery of our services.
Use of Websites
We use cookies on our websites. These cookies are used to help track where you go on our websites so we can better understand how best to serve you. If you log in to a CableLabs website account or arrive at one of our websites through clicking on a link we provided in an email or other communication the cookie will be linked to the data we have about you. IP addresses are collected from website visitors and processed through commercial data analytic software,, but are not identified with you or your information.
You may turn off the cookie feature through your browser and will still be able to access the website.
Data Subject Rights
The European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation and other countries’ privacy laws may provide you with certain rights with regards to what data we can collect about you and what we can do with this data.
This Privacy Notice is intended to provide you with information about what personal data the CableLabs or a subsidiary may collect about you and how it is used. If you have any questions, please contact us.
If you wish to confirm whether we are processing your personal data, or to access any personal data CableLabs or a subsidiary may have about you, please contact us.
You may also request information about: the purpose of the processing; the categories of personal data concerned; who else outside CableLabs or its subsidiaries might have received the data from us; what the source of the information was (if you didn’t provide it directly to us); and how long it will be stored. You have a right to correct (rectify) the record of your personal data we maintain if it is inaccurate. You may request that we erase that data or cease processing it, subject to certain exceptions. You may also request that we cease using your data for direct marketing purposes. In many countries, you have a right to file a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority if you have concerns about how we process your personal data. When technically feasible, we will—at your request—provide your personal data to you or transmit it directly to another controller.
Reasonable access to your personal data will be provided at no cost to you. If access cannot be provided within a reasonable timeframe, then we will provide you with a date when we can provide you with the information. If for some reason access is denied, then we will provide an explanation as to why access has been denied.
Data Security, Storage, and Retention
To help protect the privacy of data and personally identifiable information you may transmit through the use of our websites we maintain physical, technical and administrative safeguards. We update and test our security technology on an ongoing basis. We restrict access to your personal data to those employees who need to know that information to provide benefits or services to you.
Your personal data is stored by CableLabs on its servers, and on the servers of the cloud-based database management services we engage, located in the United States. We retain data for the duration of your or your company’s business relationship with us. For more information on where and how long your personal data is stored, and for more information on your rights of erasure and portability, please contact us.
Payment card information
You may choose to purchase conference admission or other services from CableLabs, Kyrio, Kyrio Medical, or UpRamp using a credit card. Credit card information is provided directly by you, via our websites, into the PCI/DSS-compliant payment processing service to which we subscribe. Neither CableLabs, Kyrio, Kyrio Medical nor UpRamp processes or stores any credit card information.
If you have any questions about your personal data privacy, what information we hold, how to change or update to that information, how to change how we communicate with you, how to remove your data from our records, or any other concern please contact us.
At cablelabs.com, we use cookies to improve your experience on our website. By browsing our website, you agree to our use of cookies.
Privacy Preferences
I Agree
